And yes, it's easy to think.
是的 答案显而易见
Let's forget about the one that always lies.
我们可以先排除这个总是说谎的朋友
And in real life, maybe that's a good thing.
在现实生活中这种人可能很坏
But in here, we could really get good information out of this one.
但在这儿 我们能从中得到非常有用的信息
What if we ask this friend a lot of yes/no questions.
如果我们总是问这个朋友正确与否的问题
Well, we'll always get the wrong answers,
那我们就总是得到错误答案
so all we have to do is do the exact opposite.
所以我们要做的就是采纳相反的答案
In this way, the complete liar gives us a lot of information.
这样我们就能从这个骗子那里得到大量有用的信息了
In contrast, the one who lies half of the time doesn't really help
相反 那个一半真话一半谎话的朋友并不能够帮到多少忙
us much since we have no idea if we should believe them or not.
因为我们没法判断是否应该相信他
And obviously, the truthful one is super helpful, too.
当然 那个总是说真话的朋友也非常有用
So, we conclude that the worst one is this one in the middle.
因此我们得出结论 最糟糕的应该就是中间的这位
In the same way, we'll have our three models.
同样 我们的三个模型中
Model one is the truthful one,
模型一是真实模型
which is always correct.
它总是正确的
Model two is the random one,
模型二一半情况下是正确的
which is correct roughly half of the time.
所以是个随机模型
And model three is a liar, which is always wrong.
模型三总是错误的 所以是个虚假模型
So, what we'll do is we'll assign the truthful model a large positive weight,
所以 我们要给第一个模型赋予较大的正权重值
the random model a weight of zero since it's useless,
给第二个模型赋予 0 权重值 因为它没有作用
and the liar model
赋予第三个模型较大的负权重值
a large negative weight since we'll do the exact opposite as this model says.
因为我们要采纳的是与这个模型建议相反的决策
So, here's a bit of math. We have our number line and
这可能牵扯到数学知识 现在有一条数轴
we want our weight function to look like this.
我们希望权重函数是这样的走向
Super positive for the truthful models,
真实模型是正无穷
zero for the useless models,
第二个模型是 0
and super negative for the liar models.
虚假模型是负无穷
Let's remember how the models look.
我们回忆一下三个模型的样式
They look like this.
分别是这样
And let's look at the accuracy.
我们看一下它们的准确率
The truthful model has accuracy around one,
真实模型的准确率大约在 1
the random model has accuracy around 50 percent,
随机模型的准确率大约是 50%
and the liar model has accurate around zero.
虚假模型的准确率大约是 0
So this function will help us check it out.
所以这个函数能帮我们得到
Y equals natural logarithm of x divided by one over x,
Y 等于 X 除以 1 减 X 所得商的自然对数
where x is the accuracy.
X 代表准确率
Check this out. It's very negative for values close to zero.
检查一下 数值逼近 0 时 这个结果是负无穷
For 0.5, it's logarithm of 0.5 divide by 0.5,
数值是 0.5 时 结果是 0.5 除以 0.5 所得商的自然对数
which is logarithm of one, which is zero.
也就是 1 的自然对数 为 0
And finally, is very positive for values close to one.
如果数值接近 1 那么结果是正无穷
There are actually much heavier mathematical reasons for this
还有很多数学原因解释这个函数
to be the function but that's outside the scope of this course.
但那不属于本课程的范畴
In the instructor comments,
在讲师注释板块
we'll link some reading material including
我们会上传一些相关阅读材料
the original paper by Froyin and Shapir, if you're curious.
包括 Freund 和 Schapire 的论文原稿 供大家阅读
And if your head is spinning and your alarms are going off because
如果你觉得晕头转向
you saw potential division by zero, don't worry.
发现除数可能为 0 别担心
We'll deal with that in a bit.
我们之后会讲到
So, we conclude that a great formula for weight is this.
所以 我们的结论是权重公式如下
Natural logarithm of accuracy divided by one minus accuracy.
准确率 除以 1 减准确率 所得商的自然对数
So, a small quiz. Can you find the weights for these three models over here?
做个小测试 你能得出这三个模型每个的权重吗？
Enter your answers below..
请将你的答案写在下方